[
  {
    "question": "Your Reliable and Trusted Transport Services Provider",
    "answer": "ShipMates is dedicated to offering high-quality and cost-effective transport services to various business owners in India. We aim to reduce the gap between the customers and manufacturers/traders through our hassle-free and quick transportation services. Our online booking platform has simplified the process of hiring trucks to transport your goods from one city to another. We manage the highest number of trucks, which are more than 20 lakhs Trucks, for shipping goods across PAN-India.We have introduced a user-friendly and advanced online booking and cost estimation too through which customers can book and calculate their estimated costs in no time. So, if you are looking for a genuine truck transporter for your business, you can count on us. You can speed up your transportation process with our end-to-end support and quick online truck booking platform"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who We Are",
    "answer": "Established in 2017, ShipMates offers premium goods transportation services to thousands of business owners in Delhi NCR. With our transparent, reliable, and affordable booking option, we intend to simplify the transportation of goods to various businesses. With us, you don't need to waste your time & money on brokers, and you can instantly get the trucks to transport your business's goods. We have all categories of open, container, and trailer trucks shipping across PAN-India."
  },
  {
    "question": "What We Do",
    "answer": "ShipMates is dedicated to resolving day-to-day business operations and transportation concerns through our affordable and top-notch services, specially made for India. So, if you are looking for transport services, you can check our services committed to boosting your business growth by speeding up your supply chain logistics."
  },
  {
    "question": "PAN INDIA TRUCK BOOKING",
    "answer": "We offer an advanced and user-friendly online truck booking platform to provide different business owners with safe and quick transportation solutions. Our more than 20 lakh trucks running from Delhi NCR to PAN India are always here for you to offer a rich industry experience at the best price. We enable thousands of large businesses to make data-driven decisions by delivering actionable insights"
  },
  {
    "question": "Over 20 Lakhs Vehicles",
    "answer": "Get your goods delivered on time without wasting your money and time. We have more than 20 lakhs verified trucks available in different sizes and types to fulfill all your"
  },
  {
    "question": "Competitive Prices",
    "answer": " We understand that finding genuine truck transportation services within your budget is not an easy task. That's why to save your efforts and money, we provide high-quality transportation services at the best price in the market."
  },
  {
    "question": "Quick Booking",
    "answer": "Why spend hours to find the estimated cost and then book the trucks when you can do this within a few clicks? We provide an easy-to-use and hassle-free platform through which you can check the estimated pricing and find a perfect deal for your desired locations."
  },
  {
    "question": "24/7 Customer Support",
    "answer": "Need help? Have any emergencies? No worries, our transport company is here to help. Our friendly and helpful customer support executives are always at the helpdesk to resolve your concerns. We'd love to help you."
  },
  {
    "question": "Fast and Reliable Services",
    "answer": "Customer satisfaction is our utmost priority. We always strive to provide the highest quality of services quickly and without any hassle. Our track record of happy customers is proof of our top-notch transport services."
  },
  {
    "question": "Get The Best Transport Services In India",
    "answer": "We are experienced in providing on-demand transportation solutions to various business owners. Our Full Truck Load (FTL) services are perfect and most profitable to fulfill the logistic needs of your business. Our online truck booking app will not help you save time, but also help you save money by providing you with reliable solutions. So, get our Full truckload services and enjoy maximum profit and business growth"
  }
]
